# **Daniel Evans**

Bristol Based Junior Web Developer

Portfolio: https://daniel-jj-evans.github.io/portfolio/

Github: <a href="https://github.com/daniel-jj-evans">https://github.com/daniel-jj-evans</a>

## Profile

Full stack web developer with experience in building small scale web applications. My skill set includes knowledge of Javascript ES6+ and ReactJs and i am looking forward to learning and developing my skills within my next role.

I am a responsible and engaging team player who is open minded and adaptable. I am calm in complex and difficult situations that require teamwork, practical solutions, critical thinking, analysis and a good attention for detail. I approach tasks methodically and creatively.

In my spare time I enjoy gaming in which i am very competative usually playing fps or mmo genre of games other than gaming i also enjoy traveling to new countries and cooking.

# Experience

#### **Junior Web Developer**

Sept 2020 to Nov 2020

An intesive 12 week remote course in full stack software development, that included a client project that ran for jsut over 4 weeks in which we worked collabrativly in small teams along side a client to produce a fully function app. We worked using weekly sprints where we assigned project managers for that week and daily stand ups and retrospectives.

We had one week dedicated to soft skills training where we learned about work ethic and working in an agile dev team also focusing on remote working and how to be more effecient and effective working in a remote environment.

# Skills

**Software Development:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, Git, Bash, NPM/Yarn, Rest API's, Postman, Authentication & Authorization, Unit testing, (Jest & Enzyme).

Front end Libraraies and Frameworks: SASS, React, Bootstrap, Angular.

Back end development: Firebase(Auth, Database and storage), NodeJs and Express

# **Work Experience**

#### Care Assistant - Social Care

July 2018 to Aug 2020

My main responsibilities in this role were:

- Accessing and recording patient information in clinical management information systems (MIS)
- Checking and dispensing medication to clients.
- Booking and attending appointments with patients ensuring confidentiality.
- Assisting with managing client's finances when needed.
- Ensuring patients are up and ready for their day ensuring they have adequate activities and opportunities to go out with support. Patients require sensitivity and a calm demeanor.
- Assisting with any hygiene or personal care support required on a day-to-day basis.
- Safeguarding

#### **Bray Leino Advertising - Bristol**

Aug 2013 Assisted PR department in preparing for campaigns

### **Bristol Central Library**

June 2011 Supporting staff in general library duties

## Education

# **Cardiff Metropolitan University**

Sept 2015 to June 2018 Fine Art - 2:1

**SGS College - Bristol** 

Sept 2014 July 2015

**Cotham / Redland Green Sixth Form - Bristol** 

**Cotham Secondary School - Bristol**